Alan Shirley
Lorraine
看來我們最終
還是要冤家聚下頭啊
這剛由法庭發派下來給我們
沒錢的當事人
上個律師被公交撞了
現在他得要個新律師
你是不是沒犯這罪行?
你幹嗎不向法庭求情
了結這個案子?
他是清白的
Alan 你來接手這個
我? 那Jerry呢?
就算有一線希望
也不在Katie Lloyd身上
Katie Lloyd將成為我的律師
Rivers醫生 很多人聲稱
Joseph Washington迷戀過您妻子
- 你看出過跡像麼?
- 沒有
我總覺得他是個好人
在我們國家有個原則叫"無罪假定"
但是我覺得你們都不會假定
Joseph Washington是清白的
我是說 想想吧
他被逮捕帶到法庭上
因為警察和地方檢察官都深信他有罪
鑒於先要起訴
在座的12位或許各持己見
即使在被告還沒有為自己申辯
你們就已經...
停下
為什麼要做讓步?
我覺得最好先站在他們的立場上
解釋"認為他有罪是合理的"
永遠不要讓你當事人看起來有罪
而且永遠不要給陪審團這樣想的餘地
警察揪住Joseph Washington
不過因為他們找不到其他人
所以我們才派上用場
一個富有醫生的妻子
在治安良好的社區被殺
有人必須坐牢 不管是否抓對了人
如果我們承認"好吧 他看起來有罪"
不是更顯得我們的可信麼?
但是有罪 是個法律詞 Katie
是指起訴的目的最終達到
也許你該來做
我本可以 但當事人指明了要你
或者 或者由Jerry
不 就得你
10個小時候後
你就要開始了
你到底是不是個律師?
- 我是個律師
- 是的 沒錯
當你說 "釋放我的當事人吧"
坐這欄內的12個人得相信你才行
如果你自己都不相信自己
那麼這是天方夜譚
我們可以從頭再聽一次麼?
好的
早上好 女士們先生們
我們國家有個原則叫 "無罪假定"
我沒事
哦 天啊
-=伊甸園美劇 http://sfile.ydy.com=-
榮譽出品
本字幕僅供學習交流 嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=-
時間軸: 卡肉肉 小野人王
翻譯: hislily gengen
校對: sade
波士頓法律
第四季 第2集
你說她暈倒了 什麼意思?
她並未完全喪失知覺--但是
她現在在哪兒？
在法庭 她提前去那裡適應去了
Jerry呢?
嘰裡咕嚕了一路
他得詢問第一個證人
以給Katie點適應的時間
然後他會做結案陳詞
Alan 他們會有勝算麼?
如果他們能證明
當事人和受害人是情人
可能會有機會將嫌疑指向
受害人丈夫
他們能證明麼?
如今他們只有當事人的一面之詞
Katie今天要去見
受害人的心理醫生
也許他能證實
我得上庭了
Alan 等等
我首先得告訴你點事
- 又有誰告你了麼?
- 沒 沒人
只是 因為Denise產假延長
而這裡事情又忙了點兒
我已經僱傭了另一位合作人
太好了 我希望 是個女人
是的
喜歡被招惹和挑逗的女人
喜歡啊
那我等不及要見她呢
其實是 你已經見過她了
Lorraine 這位是Alan
Alan 這位是Lorraine
你好啊 Alan
看上去還是不錯嘛
這 這開玩笑麼?
恩 這不是玩笑
她是個很棒的律師
這 這也許有點意思 但不是個玩笑
但有點意思 對誰來說呢?
也許對我來說吧 也許Lorraine
能賞識其中的幽默 是不 Lorraine?
是個很殘忍的死法
勒頸導致氣管破裂
就是 喉嚨那裡
讓壓力擠到眼槽
所以有時候眼睛會像大家知道的
那樣爆出來
死亡過程大概要2分鐘
我覺得 除非是個特別反社會變態
才會這麼殘忍殺人
我們不該叫 反對 麼?
我覺得還是不要啦
我是說 想想吧 看著你的受害人
你把她生命奪走的時候
還盯著她眼睛
你看著她深受痛苦
這是墮落的本質啊
謝謝你 醫生
你的證詞參雜了心理學的成分
你是個心理學家麼 醫生?
不是
你是個行為分析學家麼?
那我好奇你幹嗎
不僅就醫學證據來論理
你有任何醫學證據
來證明我當事人就是兇手麼?
他的精子在那女人體內
那是有過性關係的證據
不是謀殺證據
是強姦證據
你採集到的證據能證實
有強姦的行為發生嗎 醫生?
陰道有淤痕
根據你報道 是小陰道有腫
兩相情願的性關係也會這樣
不是麼?
我想是的
沒問題了
你坐在後面幹嗎呢?
我在監督呢
你現在有答案了麼?
什麼的答案?
我們的孩子
我們要不要一個?
Gloria 我覺得要不要孩子是個改變
一生的決定
你真的要催促我嗎?
考慮到這事關...
- 於我?
- 是的
我們已經在一起很長時間了
你要還是不要?
把我逼成那樣 你能想像嗎?
女人有這麼一特點 Alan
她們腦細胞和卵子會一起流失
而這個女人的問題所在就是...
- 她神精了
- Gloria?
她簡直就是瘋婆娘 相信我
當然 你又顯然好瘋婆娘那一口
打擾下
- 有空吃飯不?
- 我有
Denny 你能為我們迴避下不?
我知道有個很不錯的餐廳
我們現在走吧
我們可以坐電梯哦
Denny 求你啦
歡迎來著律所
我是Denny Crane
- 很榮幸見到你
- 天啊
我也是
我不會窺探你
如果你擔心這個的話
為什麼你來這裡
帶著那樣美麗的脖子和眼睛
還有這一切?
我是來從事法律 Alan
別擔心我
我們要擔心你麼?
- 我們不能這麼做
- 永遠不
很感謝你願意見我 醫生
我不肯定能不能幫到你
我知道你治療Rivers夫人
大約有3年了
是的
而在這期間 她有沒有提到和
Joseph Washington的親密關係?
Lloyd小姐 病人告訴我的
所有事情都要保密
肯定你是知道的
當然
醫生 我非常敬慕
你堅守保密的精神
但我的當事人被誤控以謀殺
如果我不能證實這段地下情
至少現在無法證實...他很可能會被定罪
我有點絕望啊
很抱歉
如果你被傳喚到法庭上
我能指望你會說實話麼?
律師啊
真相是什麼 你想都想不到
那東西難吃死了
對街有很好的濃咖啡 好得多
讓 讓我帶你去吧
我們可以坐電梯下去
再坐電梯回來
Alan告訴了你我們的一些過往
嗯 他那是出於罪惡感
他需要朋友的安慰
他現有一段非常認真的戀情
你知道吧
你的手放在我臀上
無意的接觸啦
聽著 Alan在專一這方面有問題
他卻對朋友衷心不二
比如說 他永遠不會背叛我
但是女人嘛
我當然盡力幫他啦
他有你在身邊可真幸運
總之 即使有Gloria他也無法抗拒你
這翹起的唇 這誘人的胸部
唯一他會對你罷手的方法是
你和他...
他親密的朋友有染
比如說他的最好朋友
比如說 我
你站得太近了 Denny
和我上床吧
為了Alan
那麼你到現場時 受害者就是
這個狀態和方位嗎 警探?
是的 我們立刻認定是勒死的
你們當即有發現什麼線索嗎 長官
鄰居看到看門人Joseph Washington
大概下午5點進了案發現場
在搜他櫥櫃時 我們找到了
和受害人的血跡
在審問被告過程中
他承認了強姦並殺害Rivers夫人
D.N.A.檢測也證實了精子是他的
謝謝你 長官
你能成不?
是的
我想問下 血是從Washington先生
的櫥櫃外還是櫥櫃內找到的?
外面
所以如果有人想造成
Joseph Washington殺了她的假象
他們弄兩滴上去就可以了?
但他也坦白了
是的 我知道
他為自己清白捍衛了36小時
而這36小時內他毫無睡眠
後來他才主動招認
他招認的內容是
"好吧 我幹的 管他呢"
是自願的 真實的
- 你們還考慮了其他人嗎?
- 沒有
有人目擊他在案發時間
進入她公寓
所以他立刻吸引了我的注意力
一經檢驗精子是他的
櫥櫃上血是她的
他就成了我們唯一嫌疑犯
而且他認罪了
所以他是你們唯一真正調查的?
你在哪找到這個Katie的?
不是所有好的年輕律師
都出自哈佛 Alan
那她是哪兒畢業的?
哈佛
那麼我們--我們會不會多個孩子?
Denny告訴我啦
你以前有沒有在生孩子
這個問題上困惑過 Shirley?
問題是你不想要孩子 Alan
還是不想和Gloria生孩子?
我家裡的父輩都不怎麼樣
我太祖父
我祖父
我父親
一代不如一代
而我 也是
你覺得你做不了好爸爸?
我覺得讓養育一個孩子
他肯定會充滿困惑
Jerry?
很抱歉打擾
Alan 我們得出發了
好的
Shirley 失陪
我就在6點前進了我們公寓
我叫Ann的名字 但是沒人回應
這很奇怪因為我們約好了
要早點去晚餐
我到了起居室看到了她
她的眼睛張開 暴突
她已經死了
先生 你想到可能是誰行兇的嗎?
我早知道誰會這麼做
Joseph Washington
為什麼 醫生?
我妻子最近一直向我抱怨
他對她有圖謀不軌
她覺得他是迷戀上了
而她又很害怕他
為什麼他要說那樣的謊話?
我以前特意問了他
"你有任何懷疑Joseph的理由嗎?"
而他說 "沒有"  你聽到的 Jerry
是的 騙子 騙子!
- 好的 你們倆都深呼吸一下
- 騙子！
Jerry 別動!
證人會撒謊 這人就是如此
或許因為他是真正的兇手
或者控方就告訴他
他們在行兇動機上站不住腳
而他決定給他們出把力
大家都知道丈夫殺害妻子
的兇手有偏恨
我沒有殺她
那麼我該怎麼做?
你可以叫Jerry證實他騙人 然而這樣
他會作為證人而不是律師出庭
換了我 就會控訴那醫生說謊
讓他證詞動搖
我還可以問問他是否知道
他妻子和Joseph有地下情
這是推測一個沒有證據的案情
不過那又怎樣?
這問題本身就是贏點
然後在時間方面詢問他
我要指責他是兇手嗎?
要是我 我就不會
你又證明不了
我們不能讓你唱黑臉
因為Joseph對你的人品如此死心塌地
- 聽起來並不夠啊
- 你證據也不夠啊
你所能利用的就是合理存疑
而你們必須要保持冷靜
我和你談話的時候 醫生
你可沒說過任何你妻子害怕什麼的話
事實上
你說她對我當事人毫無抱怨
我自己決定不和某些
想讓強姦和謀殺
我妻子的兇手逍遙法外的人合作
醫生 你知道你妻子和
Joseph Washington有段地下情嗎?
我不知道
你說你在6點前進入了你公寓
是的
停車庫的監控器上
顯示你是5點20進去的
你這40分鐘做了什麼 醫生?
和某同僚在手機上
聊了一個腫瘤學案例
這段時間我在做記錄和總結
醫生 是不是你殺了你妻子
又想嫁禍給我當事人?
- 法官大人
- 反對無效
我沒殺我妻子
你好像並未覺得
此問題有冒犯性
我對這問題不詫異是因為
當你來我辦公室時就露出了底牌
你顯露出你的目的 律師
我沒有其他問題了
沒有問題了 法官大人
你可以下去了 醫生
Chase先生?
控方沒有其他問題了 法官大人
真是對不起
我只是-我覺得交叉提問的內容
太沒有力度了
我記得你的忠告
問題本身也是贏點
而我就突然冒出指控他的念頭
你不記得我建議你不要唱黑臉?
好吧
Joseph
看著我
我覺如果求情的話
二級謀殺依舊可以申請到
- 現在應該是時候
- 不
我可以出庭
這樣的話你的前科也會被抖出來
那 我也不會認罪
我沒殺她 我不會說我殺了她的
那樣我還不如餘生入獄
我不會那麼說
受害者的心理醫生呢?
我傳喚了他
我不知道他會說什麼
你有什麼直覺不?
我覺得他會說實話
- 就是說出他們實際上是情人這事實
- 是的
如果你不知道一個證人要說什麼
就不應該叫他/她上庭
但是?
但是我覺得你現在別無選擇
你能以上帝之名宣誓說出真相
及所有真相並絕無虛言?
- 是的
- 請入座
下午好 Wood醫生
首先要指出
你是因為法庭傳喚而到庭
- 對不對?
- 是的
你執業期間
是否治療過Ann Harris Rivers?
是的
不用洩露內容的前提下 請告訴我們
她有說過她婚姻的事情麼?
說過
也許你該到此為止
是的 但是你讓我覺得
你是個很有原則的人
- 而且要讓一個清白的人進監獄的話
- 反對
反對有效
醫生 Rivers夫人和你提到
我當事人Joseph Washington嗎?
是的
而她說了什麼?
法官大人 她要證人
打破保密條例
病人已經死了 保密條例可取消
我允許問這個問題
醫生 Rivers夫人告訴你
Joseph Washington的什麼事情
請回答這個問題 醫生
她說她和Washington先生是情人
我沒有其他問題了
我又沒建議她
我只是要求她和我上床
Denny 如果我要Shirley和我上床
你會是什麼感受?
Shirley 是我一生的最愛
Lorraine只是
你在電梯裡大搞特搞的女人
不不不不 她不止不止
我不希望你去挑逗她
好吧
Gloria最近怎樣?
- 我不要談Gloria
- 我要
你什麼時候打算告訴她
你真愛的是Lorraine?
Lorraine是段地下情罷了
這和正式交往有大不同了
是的 地下情一般更持久
- 看看現在誰才是憤世嫉俗的人?
- 我是啊
你是浪漫主義者 你愛Lorraine
- 我才不愛--
- 打擾一下
你--你說你想見我
是的
Denny剛好要出去
- 沒啊 我沒有
- 是的 你就是
門上可要寫上 "暗礁四伏"
(電影的名字)
Katie
在聽過心理醫生的證詞之後
我認為你有足夠證據
提出"合理懷疑"
是嗎?
是的
現在的問題是
是否讓Joseph出庭作證
他是唯一能解釋為什麼認罪的人
是的 但是一旦他去作證
他過去犯罪記錄就會潮水般湧來
這就是為什麼我的直覺
告訴我不要讓他作證
但是我的直覺卻的正好相反
對不起
Katie 他的舉止
並不討好
我第一眼看見他的時候
我看到的是一頭野獸
陪審團可能也這麼看他
而且…而且可能仍舊這麼看他
但是當我聽他訴說
當我和他談話
我看到了他人性的一面
信不信由你 他很有風度
我想讓陪審團也看到他的這一面
我要讓他們認識到
這個男人是多麼的有人性
你真的認為他是清白的
我確信
那就讓他出庭作證吧
我們的關係必須要極其保密
她不想讓任何人發現
我們一直在她的公寓見面
她死的那天晚上
你去過公寓
我剛好在5點之前到公寓
在快6點的時候離開
你在那兒的時候發生了什麼?
我們在幽會
你們做愛了
是的
Washington先生 她死後警察逮捕了你
而你承認了罪行
你能告訴我們為什麼嗎?
警察闖進我家 說我殺了人
把我關進一個房間裡
他們連續兩天讓我一直醒著
給我喝咖啡 不讓我睡覺……
你告訴他們你和
受害人是情人了嗎?
他們根本不想聽這些
他們一直說只要我承認是我做的
就放我出去
最終 我…
我放棄了
你知道 他們已經認定是我幹的了
我只想讓他們放過我
所以我說"隨便你們了"
然後他們給我找了個律師
他也不想知道真相
他只想讓我認罪
這樣他就可以收工了
他之後的律師也是這樣
再之後的也是
就是說你承認了
你根本沒有犯的罪
我承認了我根本沒有犯的罪
Washington先生
你在1985年曾被判有強姦罪?
約會強姦
我是清白的
- 我……
- 你被判有罪 是或否？
我想解釋清楚
請
她當時16歲
我17
她是我女朋友 而且她是白人
她父親
走了進來
正好撞見我們在……
她……
她說是我強姦她的 但是我沒有
那麼你確實在1985年
被判有強姦罪
你在1989年被判有持槍搶劫罪?
當時我有毒癮
你在1989年被判有持槍搶劫罪
是或否?
是的
你在1991年被判
威脅侵犯他人身體罪
我在監獄裡受到了攻擊
我只是自衛反擊
就是說你在這些案件裡
你並非被誤判?
你的儲物櫃上
怎麼會有Rivers太太的血?
有人弄上去的
我...我是被陷害的
是嗎?血跡通過顯微鏡才能看到
如果有人想要陷害你
不是應該弄得肉眼也能看到嗎?
不管是誰要陷害我
他很精明
瞭解了
那麼
回顧一下 你沒殺人
你是被陷害的
你沒有強姦
受害人假裝的
搶劫是因為你磕了藥
人身侵犯是自衛
我愛Ann Rivers
因愛成恨
噢 你可不想聽到這個
- 法官大人
- Washington先生 沒有…
警察也不想聽到這個
所有人都只想聽我承認殺了她
我沒有殺她
我不在乎
你們是不是認定是我幹的
我沒有奪走這個女人的性命!
Joseph
我並未犯下這項罪行
Lorraine
都安頓好了?
是的 謝謝
覺得一切都還好?
覺得Denny沒什麼吧?
Denny總是來找我
我會讓他注意的
好的
還有什麼事嗎?
Jerry
已經快半夜了
我正在給自己想造型
想好了嗎?
我在考慮用木製香煙
沒有它我就心神不定
有了這根假煙 你表現不錯
但是我認為你…你…
你在按照自己方式說話的時候
才是狀態最好的時候
你明天要做出最好的表現 Jerry
你不能靠玩花樣來贏官司
你要發自內心的和他們對話
你相信你的當事人嗎?
相信
我真的相信
那麼 明天你只要相信你自己就好了
你對Shirley說的那些是錯的
你說什麼?
我認為你會成為一個好父親
我想像不出比你更好的父親
來指引孩子了
謝謝你 Jerry
我想如果我們相信
Washington的證詞
那他可就是我認識的最倒霉的人
在高中和女友約會
女友為了避免惹老爸生氣告他強姦
那是很倒霉
染上毒隱 為了有錢磕藥
不得不去搶劫
又是運氣差
在監獄裡 他又不得不把
一個男人的腦袋打開花
另一個不幸遭遇
和他通姦的女人剛好被殺
正好就在他們不論是自願
還是強迫的的性交之後
他還能再倒霉點嗎?
事實上
還能
在他的儲物櫃上發現了她的血跡
到底奇怪在什麼地方呢?
在他遇到這麼多霉運之後
肯定不該在這個時候承認
自己未犯的罪行 不是嗎?
現在他們多麼可悲
多麼喪心病狂 竟然卑劣的轉而指控
受害人那飽受痛苦的鰥夫
但是我猜這種做法也和他們的那些
邏輯是一致的 不是嗎?
兇手不是有暴力傾向 前科滿滿
並最後一個與死者接觸的男人
而成了這位無前科 無動機
而又以治癒癌症為生的男士?
我們逮捕Joseph Washington因為
我們邪惡
現在你們需要走進那個房間
決定誰才是邪惡的一方
Washington先生今天在這兒
不是因為他倒霉
他
犯下了
謀殺罪
事實是 當警方和控方堅持
強姦罪行的存在時
他們忽略了我的當事人和受害人是情人
關係的這一事實 他們確實是
Rivers太太的主治醫生可以證實
Joseph Washington一直在重申的話
而警方一直拒絕考慮這一點
事實上 我的當事人並不是案發時
唯一在現場的人
Rivers醫生也在
事實是 他在我的當事人離開前40分鐘
就進入了公寓大樓
他說他留在車裡
紀錄筆記
或許他是在等待時機 等待那個和自己
妻子有染的男人離開
Chase先生堅持說
Rivers先生沒有殺人動機
那根本不是事實
如果他知道妻子對自己不忠
就足以構成動機
實際上Rivers先生
從來沒有告訴過警察
他在大樓裡等了足足40分鐘
他沒告訴任何人
是我們看監控錄像發現的
事實就是 他說謊
在問他關於Joseph Washington的問題時
他承認自己撒了謊
事實就是
訴訟方無法排除他是殺手的可能
事實就是 正如Berenson警探的證詞
警方沒有調查除我當事人以外的任何人
因為他們認定Joseph Washington有罪
警方 訴訟方
他們也是人 他們也犯錯誤
在這他們就犯了一個
如果控方要讓被告被判有罪
必須要排除合理疑問 證明其有罪
這是非常高的標準
也正是我們向來恪守的標準
我們設立這個標準 是因為
一旦我們降低標準 任由人們被定罪
監獄裡關著的人不只是罪犯
也關進了清白的人
想想看 一個無辜的人要為他
沒做過的事而失去生活
今天我們這就坐著一位清白的男人
許多人去念法學院都
憧憬著這樣一個特權
就是哪一天能在法庭上
為無辜的人伸張正義
我真心的感到 今天能在這裡為
Joseph Washington辯護是我的榮幸
就算你們已傾向於判他有罪
就像訴訟方認定的那樣
你們必須承認合理疑點的存在
與此同時 這還有一個人
一個有殺人動機的人
一個並未完全向警方坦白的男人
一個承認向我們說謊的人
一個在車裡等到Joseph Washington
離開的人
你們就是不能否認
合理疑點的存在
你朋友的結案陳詞很震撼
是的
我不能和你生孩子 Gloria
好吧
我愛過的每個女人 我都不再愛了
但是有了個孩子
我會盡力安定下來
隨著日子週而復始一天天過去
我會變得
越來越 越來越
不像我自己
再見 Alan
再見
通常這需要多久?
時間不等
不論結果怎樣
我都要謝謝你們兩個
不久前 我已經喪失了
別人會相信我 對我有信心的這個念頭
他們要宣判了
- 什麼?
- 才30分鐘
我們走吧
我首先要警告每個人
宣讀判決之後
我不容許法庭出現任何混亂場面
判決達成一致?
是的
辯護方請起立
我提醒大家 總共有兩項指控
在陪審員把兩項判決都宣佈之前
請控辨雙方不要過早的慶祝
陪審員先生 你們的判決是?
在馬薩諸塞州
對Joseph washington以一級謀殺
的罪名指控中
陪審團判定被告
無罪
在馬薩諸塞州
對Joseph Washington以二級謀殺
的罪名指控中 陪審團判定被告
無罪
陪審團成員們 你們完成了使命
被告無罪釋放
退庭
恭喜 Katie
謝謝
幹得漂亮 Jerry
Joseph 你聽到最後那部分了嗎?
你自由了
結束了?
太及時了 我快要吐了
謝謝你
太感謝你了
讓我們喘口氣 成不
你們這些粘住人不放的傢伙?
你們想這樣就走掉?
不好意思
請你不要離開司法管轄區域
- 看在上帝的分上
- 我們受的罪還不夠多嗎?
這麼做有問題嗎?
沒有
我真不敢相信他們贏了
Denny你應該看看Jerry的表現
他太出色了
新來的女孩也是
你和Gloria做朋友草草了事?
不
真令人難過  你們怎麼能從
親密無間突然轉為漠然相對
我是說 人生中有多少個
讓你念念不忘?
卻又突然間音訊全無的知己?
真淒慘
Alan
或許Lorraine來這兒是有理由的
我和她不可能的
絕對不可能
我在想我就是那個理由
我討厭什麼先來後到的
應該有個條例限制一下...
根本沒有
我保證
我永遠不會和Bev或者Bethany亂搞
或者Shirley
Shirley有主了
你說什麼?
你從來沒想過Carl Sack
來這兒的理由是什麼嗎?
Shirley
和Carl Sack一起?
我可以和你打賭
我要殺了他
你確定?
確定
我想我接受不了
我…還愛她
在我心中我…我…我…
我仍然相信
她就是我命中注定的另一半
你都有過5…6個老婆
無所謂多少個了
你還相信什麼"命中注定"?
對我來說這是唯一重要的信仰
Shirley
和Carl Sack
或許她是在利用Carl Sack忘記我
肯定是這樣的
愛情這檔子事太險惡
老友 太險惡
但是我們卻靠它活著
像你說的那樣
也許它是唯一重要的事了
險惡的愛情
-------------------------------
本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=-
時間軸: YTET- 卡肉肉 小野人王
翻譯: hislily gengen
校對: sade
Alan,shirley.
Lorraine.
I suppose it was inevitable
we'd finally bump heads a bit.
This was just assigned
to us by the court.
Indigent client-- old lawyer
jumped in front of a bus--
now he needs a new one.
Did you not commit this crime?
Why aren't you pleading this case out?
He's innocent.
Alan,you take over.
Me? What about jerry?
If there's a hope,it's not katie lloyd.
Katie lloyd will be my lawyer.
Dr.Rivers,several people have stated that
joseph washington seemed obsessed with your wife.
- Did you ever see indications of this?
- No.
He always struck me as a nice man.
We have what is called a
presumption of innence in this countr
but I doubt ny of you presume
joseph washington is innocent.
I mean,when you think about it,he
was arrested and brought to trial
because the policeand the district
attorney are quite convinced he's guilty.
And since the prosecution
gets to go first,
the 12 of you might
be equally predisposed,
if you're not already,long before the
defense ever gets to present its side.
Stop.
Why make that concession?
Well,I thought better to share with them
the idea it's okay to think he's guilty--
never concede that your client looks guilty
and never give the jury permission to think so.
The police are serving up joseph
washington because they've got nobody else.
That's why we're here.
A rich doctor's wife was
killed in a safe neighborhood.
Somebody's got to go to jail,whether
it's the right person or not.
But wouldn't it help our credibility
if we admit,"okay,he looks guilty"?
But guilt is a legal term,katie.
It suggests that the
prosecution has met its burden.
Maybe you should do this.
I would,but the client insists on you.
Or--or
jerry.
No. You.
This thing starts in ten hours.
Are you a lawyer or not?
- I'm a lawyer.
- Yes,you are.
The 12 people sitting in this box need to
trust you when you say, "let my client go,"
and that will never happen
if you don't trust yourself.
Shall we listen to it from the top?
Okay.
good morning,ladies and gentlemen.
We have what is called a presumption
of innocence in this country.
I'm okay.
Oh,dear.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:卡肉肉 小野人王
Boston Legal
Season04 Episode02
what do you mean,she fainted?
She didn't completely
lose consciousness but--
where is she now?
At the courthouse. She went in early
to get comfortable with the room.
And jerry?
Purring away.
He'll take the first witness and
give katie time to find her sea legs,
and then he'll do the csing.
Alan,do--do they
have any chance here?
If they can establish that the
client and the victim were lovers,
it may allow them to point
suspicion at the husband.
Can they establish that?
so far all they have
is the client's word.
Katie is going to see the
victim's therapist today.
Maybe he can confirm it.
I need to get to court.
Alan,wait a sec.
I just have to talk to
you about something first.
- Who's suing you
now? - N-nobody.
It's just,uh,with denise on extended
maternity and things being busier here,
I've hired another associate.
Great. A woman,I hope.
Yes.
Who likes to be teased and tempted.
Loves it.
Then I can't wait to meet her.
well,you see,you have met her.
Al-alan,lorraine. Lorraine,alan.
Hello,alan.
Still looking well.
I--is this
a joke?
Well,it's not a joke.
She's a great attorney.
I--perhaps it's a little
funny,but it's not a joke.
But funny. To whom?
Well,perhaps to me,and maybe lorraine
sees the humor in it. Do you,lorraine?
It's an extremely gruesome death.
strangulation actually
crushes the windpipe.
You know,the larynx.
it forces pressure into the eye sockets.
Sometimes the eyes have
been known to pop out.
death can take up to two minutes.
To me,I've always thought it takes a
parcular kind of sociopath to kill this way.
Shouldn't we be objecting?
I'd rather not.
I mean,think of it.
You look at your victim.
You're staring into her eyes as
you're squeezing the life out of her.
You watch her profound suffering.
It's the essence of depravity.
Thank you,doctor.
Your testimony smacked of psychology.
Are you a psychologist,doctor?
no.
Are you a behavioral scientist?
No.
I'm curious as to why you didn't
just stick to medical findings then.
Do you have any medical findings
that point to my client as the killer?
His semen was in the woman.
That's evidence of sex,not muer.
Evidence of rape.
Did your findings conclude
a rape had occurred,doctor?
There was vaginal bruising.
Minimal vaginal
bruing,according to your report,
which could be consistent with
consensual intercourse,am I correct?
I suppose.
Nothing further.
what are you doing sitting back there?
I'm monitoring.
Do you have an answer yet?
To what?
Our baby.
Are we having one?
Gloria,I suspect the decision to have a
child falls into the life-changing category.
Do you really mean to rush
me,given the fact that it'S.
- me?
- Yes.
We've been together long enough.
Are you in or out?
Can you imagine putting
it to me like that?
Well,here's the thing
about women,alan--
their eggs and their brain cells
dry up all at the same time.
And here's the thing
about that woman--
- she's a psycho.
- Gloria?
She's a total nut job. Trust me on this.
Of course,you happen to
go for total nut jobs.
Excuse me.
- Free for dinner?
- I am.
Denny,could you excuse us,please?
I know this wonderful restaurant.
We could leave right now.
We could take the elevator.
Denny,please.
Welcome to the firm.
Denny crane.
- Enchante.
- Oh,my.
me,too.
I'm not stalking you,if
that's your concern.
Why are you here,with that
neck and those eyes and.
all the rest?
I came here to practice law,alan.
No need to worry about me.
Need we worry about you?
- we can't do this.
- NeveR.
I really appreciate
you seeing me,doctor.
I'm not sure it'll do you any good.
I understand you treated mrs.
Rivers for about three years.
I did.
And during that time,did she ever mention a
romantic relationship with joseph washington?
Ms. Lloyd,anything a client
tells me is privileged.
Certainly you must know that.
Of course.
Doctor,I-I have enormous respect for
your desire to maintain confidentiality,
but I have a client I believe is
being falsely accused of murder.
If I cannot establish this affair-- and right
now I can't-- he may very well be convicted.
I'm a bit desperate.
I'm sorry.
If you were to be subpoenaed and called to the
stand,could I at least count on you to tell the truth?
Well,counselor.
you have no idea what the truth is.
That stuff'll kill you.
There's a great espresso cafe
across the street. Much better.
Le-let me take you.
We could go down in the
elevator and come back up.
Alan told you about
our little encounter.
Mm,yeah,out of guilt.
He needed the comfort of a friend.
He's in a very serious
relationship. You know this.
Your hand is on my hip.
Incidental contact.
Listen,alan has trouble with fidelity.
Oh,he can be loyal to his friends.
He would never betray me,for ample.
But womeN.
I try to help him as best I can.
Oh,he's lucky to have you.
Bottom line is he'd never be
able to resist you for gloria--
those pouty lips,come-hither breasts.
The only way he'd be able to keep his hands
off you is if you became involved with A.
a close friend.
Say his best friend.
Say me.
You're standing awfully close,denny.
Sleep with me.
for alan.
So the victim was in this condition and
position when you arrived on the scene,detective?
Yes. We immediately recognized
it as a strangulation.
Did you have any immediate leads,sir?
The neighbors saw the custodian,joseph
washington,entering the premises around 5:00 P.M.
Upon searching his locker,we found traces of
blood that ultimately matched that of the victim.
Upon questioning the defendant,he admitted
to raping and murdering mrs.Rivers.
D.N.A. Analysis eventually positively
identified the semen as being his.
Thank you,sir.
Are you okay?
yes.
if I may ask,was the blood found on the
inside or outside of mr. Washington's locker?
The outside.
So if someone had endeavored to make it
look like joseph washington had killed her,
they could've spattered
a droplet or two?
He also confessed.
Yes,as I understand it,he protested
his innocence for 36 hours,
all the while being sleep deprived,after
which he voluntarily confessed.
The extent of this confession
was,"okay,I did it.Whatever."
It was voluntary and genuine.
- Did you consider anybody else?
- No.
He was seen entering her apartment
around the time of the murder,
so our immediate focus was on him.
Once the semen was determined to be his and the
blood on his locker was determined to be hers,
he became our only suspect.
And he confessed.
So he was the only one
you really investigated?
Where'd you find this katie?
Not every great young lawyer
comes out of harvard,alan.
Where'd she come from?
Harvard.
so are-- are we
having a baby?
Denny talks.
Did you ever struggle with the
question of having children,shirley?
Is it that you don't want kids,alan,
or the idea of having them with gloria?
I come from a long line
of dreadful fathers--
my great-grandfather
and my grandfather.
my father.
With each generation,they get worse.
And me,well.
you don't think you'd
make a good father?
I think a child might get a little
lost with me leading the way.
Jerry?
I'm very sorry to intrude.
Alan,we need to go.
Right.
Shirley.
I entered our apartment
just before 6:00.
I called out to ann,but
there was no response,
which was odd because we had
planned to have an early dinner.
I went into the living
room,and there she was.
Her eyes were bulging and open.
She was dead.
Sir,did you have any thoughts about
who could've possibly done this?
I knew who did it.
Joseph washington.
and why,doctor?
My wife had recently complained to me that he had
been paying her an unusual and untoward interest.
She felt he was becoming obsessed.
And she was becoming frightened of him.
Why would he lie like that?
I specifically asked him before,"do
you have any reason to suspect joseph?"
And he said,"no." You heard him,jerry.
I did. Liar!Liar!
- Okay,both of you need to take a breath.
- Liar!
Jerry,stay.
Witnesses lie. This one did.
Either because he is the real killer,
or the prosecution simply told
him that they wobble on motive,
and he decided to bolster their case.
Husbands have been known to be
biased against their wives' killers.
I didn't kill her.
So what do I do?
Well,you can call jerry to
establish a lie,but in doing so,
he becomes a witness and would
be disqualified as a lawyer.
I would simply accuse the doctor
of lying,try to make him squirm.
I would also ask him if he knew that his
wife was having an affair with joseph.
It's assuming a fact not
in evidence,but so what?
The question itself will score.
Then cross him on time line.
Should I accuse him of being the killer?
That I wouldn't do. You can't prove it,
and we can't have you coming off as the bad guy
since joseph already seems to have that well in hand.
- It doesn't sound like much.
- You haven't got much.
All you can play for
here is reasonable doubt.
And you have got to stay calm.
when I spoke to you,doctor,you said
nothing about your wife feeling frightened.
In fact,you stated that she had
madno complaints about my client.
I had made a decision not
to cooperate with someone
who was trying to secure the freedom of
the man who had raped and murdered my wife.
Doctor,did you know that your wife and
joseph washington were having an affair?
I had no such knowledge.
You said that you went into
your apartment just before 6:00.
Yes.
Video surveillance in the parking garag
shows you entering the facility at 5:20.
What were you doing
for 40 minutes,doctor?
Finishing up a phone call with a
colleague on an oncology consult.
I spent the duration dictating
my notes and conclusions.
Doctor,did you kill your wife
and attempt to frame my client?
- Your honor-
- overruled.
I did not kill my wife.
the question didn'teem to offend you.
The question doesn't shock me because you
tipped your hand when you came to my office.
You revealed who and
what you are then,counsel.
I have nothing further.
No redirect,your honor.
You may step down,doctor.
mr.Chase?
The prosecution rests,your honor.
I'm so sorry.
I just--I felt the cross
was so utterly anemic.
D I remembered your advice about how
a question alone could be effective,
and I-I just suddenly got
the idea to accuse him.
You didn't remember the advice
about not looking like the bad guy?
Okay.
joseph.
look at me.
My guess is second degree
is still on the table.
- Now would be
the time for- - no.
I could take the stand.
In which case,all your prior
felonies will be introduced.
Well,I'm not gonna plead.
I didn't kill her. I won't say I did.
I'd rather spend the rest
of my life in jail than.
I won't say it.
What about the victim's therapist?
I subpoenaed him. I have
no idea what he'd say.
Do you have an instinct?
I think he'd tell the truth.
- The truth being they were lovers.
- Yes.
you never,ever call a witness if you
don't know what he or she is going to say.
But?
But I don't think you
have any other choice here.
Do you swear to tell the truth,the whole truth
and nothing but the truth,so help you god?
- I do.
- Be seated.
good afternoon,dr. Wood.
It should be pointed out that you
are here today courtesy of a subpoena.
- Is that correct?
- It is.
In the course of your practice,did
you treat ann harris rivers?
I did.
Without revealing content,did
she discuss her marriage?
She did.
Uh,perhaps you want to stop there.
I could. But you struck me
as a very principled man.
- And the idea of an innocent
man going to prison- - objection.
Sustained.
Doctor,did mrs. Rivers ever
discuss my client joseph washington?
She did.
And what did she say?
Your honor,she's asking the
witness to break privilege.
The patient is dead.
Privilege can be waived.
I'll allow the question.
Doctor,what did mrs. Rivers tell you
about my client joseph washington?
Please answer the question,doctor.
She said that she and mr.
Washington were lovers.
I have no further questions.
I didn't proposition her. I
merely asked her to sleep with me.
Denny,how would you feel if i
asked shirley to sleep with me?
Well,uh,shirley is the
great love of my life.
Lorraine is somebody
you rode in an elevator.
Oh,no,no,no. She's much,much.
I don't want you coming on to her.
Oh,great.
How's gloria?
I'm not talking about gloria. I am.
When are you gonna tell her
you really love lorraine?
Lorraine was an affair.
There's a big difference between
that and a committed relationship.
Yes. Affairs usually last longer.
- Oh,and now who's the cynic?
- I am.
You're the romantic. You love lorraine.
I do not love--
excuse me.
You--you said you
wanted to see me.
Yes.
Denny was ju leaving.
- No,I wasn'T.
- Yes,you were.
Big kahuna. Name on the door.
katie.
on the heels of the therapist's testimony,
I think you may have enough for reasonable doubt.
Really?
You may.
The question obviously is.
whether to call joseph to the stand.
He's the only one who can explain the confession.
True,but once he gets in that chair,the floodgates open on his priors,
which is why my gut says don't call him.
My gut says otherwise.
I beg your pardon.
Katie,he doesn't have the most.
pleasant demeanor.
When I first laid eyes on him,I saw a beast.
That may very well be what the jursaw
and--and perhaps still sees.
But when I listened to him,
when I talked to him,
I got a glimpse of his humanity.
and believe it or not,his gentility.
I'd like to afford the jury that glimpse.
I'd like them to see how deeply,deeply human this man is.
You really think you've got an innocent man here.
I know I do.
Then call him to the stand.
The affair had to be very secret.
She didn't want anybody to find out.
We always met at her apartment.
On the evening of her death,you were there.
I arrived just before 5:00 and left a little before 6:00.
And what happened whilst you were there?
We were intimate.
You made love.
Yes.
Mr.Washington,after her death,the police arrested you,and you confessed to this crime.
Can you tell us why?
The lice kicked in my door,told me I did it,put me in a room,
and then after keeping me awake for two days,
making me drink coffee,not letting me sleep--
did you tell them that you and the victim were lovers?
They didn't want to hear none of that.
They kept saying that they were not gonna let me out of that room until I said I did it.
Finally,I.
I just gave up.
You know,they had their minds all made up,and I just wanted them to leave me alone.
So I said,"whatever."
Then they gave me a lawyer,and he didn't want to hear the truth either.
He just wanted me to plead guilty so he could be done with it.
Same with the lawyer after him and the lawyer after him.
So you confessed to something you did not do.
I confessed to something I did not do.
Mr.Washington,you were convicted of rape in 1985?
Date rape.
And I was innocent.
I-- you were convicted? Yes or no?
I'd like to explain.
Go ahead.
She was 16.
I was 17.
She was my girlfriend,and she was white.
Her father.
walked in on us.
while we.
she.
she claimed that I raped her,but I did not.
So you were convicted of rape in 1985.
You were convicted of armed robbery in 1989?
I was a drug addict back then.
You were convicted of armed robbery,yes or no?
Yes.
You were convicted of aggravated assault in 1991.
I was attacked in prison.
I fought back.
So you were not at fault in any of these arrests?
How did mrs.Rivers' blood get on your locker?
Someone put it there.
I-I was framed.
Really? There were only microscopic traces.
If someone had wanted to frame you,
shouldn't it be visible to the naked eye?
Whoever did it was smart.
Got it.
So.
in review-- didn't do this one,you were framed.
You didn't commit the rape.
The victim made it up.
As for the robbery,you were on drugs.
Aggravated assault-- self-defense.
I loved ann rivers.
Move to strike.
Oh,you don't want to hear that.
- Your honor-
- mr.Washington,there's no--
the police didn't want to hear that.
All anybody wants to hear is that I killed her.
Well,I did not kill her.
And I don't care if everybody's mind is made up.
I did not take this woman's life!
Joseph.
I am innocent of this crime.
Lorraine.
Getting settled okay?
I am.Thank you.
Finding everything okay?
Finding denny okay?
Denny seems to keep finding me.
I'll speak to him.
Sure.
Anything else?
Jerry.
it's almost midnight.
I'm visualizing my closing.
You ready?
I'm thinking of using the wooden cigarette.
I'm not sure without it.
Well,you're very good with the cigarette prop.
But I think you're at your.
best when you.
speak as yourself.
You need to be at your best tomorrow,jerry.
You're not going to win this with razzle-dazzle.
Speak to them from your heart.
Do you believe in your client?
I do.
I really do.
Well,then tomorrow,you simply need to believe in yourself.
You were wrong with shirley.
I'm sorry?
I think you would make a wonderful father.
I can't imagine a better parent to lead the way.
Thank you,jerry.
I guess if we were to accept mr.Washington at his word,
he would be the most unlucky guy I know.
Dating a girl in high school,she accuses him of rape so she wouldn't get in trouble with her dad.
That's unlucky.
Becomes a drug addict,can't feed his habit unless he robs someone.
Bad break there.
In prison,he's forced to split a man's head open.
Another unfortunate bounce.
Then the woman committing adultery with him just happens to turn up dead,
and she gets killed around the same time that he's in her apartment having either consensual or nonconsensual sex with her.
Could he be any more cursed?
Well,actually.
I guess so.
Traces of her blood were found on his locker.
Now what are the odds of that?
Now with all this bad luck working against him,
this sure would be the wrong time to confess to something he didn't really do,wouldn't it?
Now how pathetic.
how desperate that they stoop to accusing the victim's grieving widower?
But I guess that falls in line with the rest of their logic,doesn't it?
I mean,it's not the man with the violent,criminal past who was last seen with her,no.
It was the man with no criminal reco,the one with no motive,the one who cures cancer for a living.
We just arrested joseph washington because we're evil.
Now you need to go into that room and decide who is evil.
Mr.Washington isn't here today because he's a little down on his luck.
He.
committed.
murder.
The fact is,while the police and the prosecution were maintaining rape,
while they summarily dismissed the notion of my client and the victim being lovers,they were.
Ms.Rivers' therapist confirmed what joseph washington had been saying all along,
what the police refused to so much as consider.
The fact is,my client was not the only person there at the time of the murder.
Dr.Rivers was there.
The fact is,he entered the building 40 minutes prior to my client leaving.
He says he remained in his car dictating some notes.
Perhaps he was biding his ti,waiting for the man he knew to be having an affair with his wife to leave.
Mr.Chase maintains dr.Rivers had no motive.
That simply is not true.
If he knew his wife was being unfaithful,that's motive.
The fact is,dr.Rivers never told the police
he'd been waiting inside the building for almost 40 minutes.
He never told anybody.
We discovered that by looking at security tapes.
The fact is,he lied.
He admitted lying to us when wquestioned him about joseph washington.
The fact is,the prosecution cannot rule him out as the killer.
The fact is,as detective berenson testified,
they never investigated anybody other than my client because they simply presumed joseph washington guilty.
The police,the prosecution,
they're human,and they make mistakes.
They made one here.
Now in order to gain a conviction,the prosecution must prove guilt beyond a reasonable doubt.
That's a very high standard,one we hold dear,
one we set because we know once we start allowing people to be convicted with less,
it doesn't simply make prison more likely for the guilty,
but the innocent as well.
And the idea of an innocent man losing his life for something he did not do.
we have such an innocent man here today.
Many of us went to law school for this very privilege,
to at least once stand up in court for the innocent man.
It is my heartfelt privilege to be representing joseph washington today.
And even if you should be so inclined as to simply presume his guilt,
as does the prosecution,you must admit reasonable doubt exists.
Another man was there at the time,a man who had motive,
a man who wasn't totally forthcoming with the police,
a man who admittedly lied to us,
a man who waited in his car until joseph washington left.
You simply cannot deny reasonable doubt exists.
Some closing from your friend.
Yes.
I can't have a child with you,gloria.
okay.
Every woman I have ever loved,I have stopped loving.
But with a child,I think I'd probably endeavor to stay.
And with each ensuing day,I would become.
less and less.
myself.
Good-bye,alan.
Good-bye.
So how long does it usually take?
It can vary.
Whatever happens.
I want to thank you,the both of you.
Not long ago,I had given up on the idea of anybody believing me,believing in me.
they've reached a verdict.
- What?
- It's been 30 minutes.
Let's go.
Let me warn everybody this room.
I will tolerate no disruption following the reading of the verdict.
This verdict is unanimous?
It is.
The defendant will please rise.
I shall remind everybody there are two counts.
Until the foreman renders the verdict on both counts,
let neither side celebrate prematurely.
Mr.Foreman,hat say you?
Inhe matter of the commonweth of massachusetts vs.
Joseph washington on the charge of murder in the first degree,
we the jury find the defendant.
not guilty.
in the matter of the commonwealth vs.
Joseph washington on t charge of murder in the second degree,we find the defendant.
not guilty.
members of the jury,this concludes your service.
The defendant is free to go.
We're adjourned.
Congratulations,katie.
Thank you.
Well done,jerry.
Joseph,did you hear the last part?
You're free to go.
It's over?
Just in time,'cause I'm about to vomit.
thank you.
Ank you so much.
give us a moment.What is it with you leeches?
Did you crowd scooter like this?
I'm sorry.
But I'd appreciate it if you didn't leave the jurisdiction,okay?
- For god sake.
- Haven't we been through enough?
Is that a problem?
No.
I can't believe they won.
Denny,you should've seen jerry.
He was brilliant.
So was the new girl.
you and gloria leave it as friends?
No.
It's sad,how you go from intimacy to nothing,cold turkey.
I mean,how many people along the way have true meaning in your life?
And to suddenly have no contact after.
it's sad.
Alan.
maybe lorraine is here for a reason.
I'm not going there.
Not a chance.
I was thinking I was the reason.
I don't like this dibs thing.
There's gotta be a statute of limitations on--
there isn'T.
You have my word.
I'll never frolic with bev or bethany.
Or shirley.
Shirley's involved.
What are you talking about?
Don't you ever wonder what carl sack's reason for being here is?
Shirley.
and carl sack?
I'd put money on it.
I'd shoot him.
You really think?
I do.
I don't think I can handle that.
I.still love her.
And in my heart,I-I-I.
I still believe she's the one.
After five or six wives-- whatever the.
count-- you still believe in "the one"?
That's the only belief that really matters.
Shirley.
and carl sack.
Maybe she's using ca sack to get over me.
Must be that.
Love is an ugly business,my friend,ugly business.
and yet we live for it.
Well,as you say,maybe it's thenly thing that really matters.
Ugly business.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET- 卡肉肉 小野人王